And we're not gonna get him out until we get close to this man.
我们要想让他出来 就必须先接近这个人
Lily-Anne,
Lilly-Anne
you look well.
你看上去很好
I don't.
我不好
Well even on your bad days, you look better than the rest of us.
你即使是在不走运的时候 看上去比我们其他人都好
You're getting the carpet cleaned?
你把地毯拿去清洗吗
It's expensive carpet.
地毯很贵
Is this what I think it is?
这情况是我想的那样吗
I'm sorry, Kaleem,
抱歉 Kallem
but I've been given no choice.
但我别无选择
We all have a choice.
我们都有选择
Your father had a choice.
你的父亲有选择
My father... was a very stubborn man.
我的父亲 非常地固执
So was my father.
我的父亲也是一样
But I didn't throw him to the wolves for it.
但我不会为此让他羊入虎口
I expect Golding will want video evidence
我想Golding需要视频记录
that you've done this yourself.
证明是你亲自动的手
You've been talking to Harry Clayton.
你和Harry Clyaton一直保持联系
That's why you have to die.
所以你必须得死
Harry Clayton is finished.
Harry Clayton完蛋了
Why do I have to die for someone
我为什么要为他而死
who won't even make it to the end of the week?
他连这个周都撑不过
If I disobey this order,
如果我不遵循这个命令
then I'm next on the hit list.
我就是下一个靶子
He'll get you anyway.
他总会抓住你的
Think,
想一想
Lily-Anne.
Lilly-Anne
Think what this will do to your conscience.
想一想你的良心过得去吗
I have no conscience left.
我已经没有良心了
You have a message for your father?
你有什么要对你父亲说的吗
You were right
你是对的
about that surveillance operation on 43 Chepstow Road.
关于切普斯托路43号的监视行动
They brought in a suspect for questioning. Twice.
他们关了一个嫌疑人 审讯了两次
Twice?
两次
A week apart.
间隔了一周
So it had been removed from the original case file.
所以它不在原来的卷宗
It would have stayed buried
如果不是你要我核查局里的记录
if you'd not made me crosscheck the station records.
它会一直被掩藏下去
It took me two days to access that. I hope it's worth it.
我花了两天的时间拿到手的 希望它可以派上用场
Thanks.
谢谢
We need to leave there now.
我们必须马上离开那
Meet me at City Hall.
我们在市政厅见
We haven't got much time.
我们的时间不多了
I think I know who Golding is.
我想我知道Golding是谁
Oi! You seen my brother? He's missing.
Oi 你看到我的弟弟了吗 他不见了
Yeah?
是吗
It's like that at Whitecross.
和Whitecross的情景一样
Here today and gone tomorrow.
今天出现了 明天不见了
Have you harmed him?
你们对他动过手吗
Us?
我们
No...
没有
We haven't touched him.
我们没碰过他
You threatened him.
你们威胁了他
We're just the foot soldiers here.
我们是无名小卒
The real power's over there.
他们才是掌权的人
Maybe you should ask him if Rich got the Rule 43,
你应该去问他 也许Rich申请了狱中保护
just like you asked for.
就像你要求过的
Where's my brother?
我的弟弟在哪儿
He's been ill.
他生病了
He's back in his cell now.
他现在回到了自己牢房
And he's been asking for you.
他一直在找你
Come on. Come with us... Come on.
来 跟我们走 来啊
Come on.
走吧
Frierson tampered with the Maria Alexandri files
Frierson篡改了Maria Alexandri的档案
to cover up who really killed her.
来掩盖真正的凶手
This should be interesting.
这下有意思了
Hello, Karl.
你好 Karl
What are you doing here, Alistair?
你来这儿做什么 Alistair
Maria Alexandri.
Maria Alexandri
You remember her, Karl?
还记得她吗 Karl
You were investigating her murder with D.I. Jim Stepton.
你当时和Jim Stepton警探调查她的凶杀案
The traveller woman,
她在旅行
stabbed in her caravan.
被人在旅行车里捅死
What has that got to do with anything?
那个案件怎么了
I crosschecked our station custody records on the Alexandri case.
我又核查了一下局里对于Alexandri案件的记录
See, some of the pages were missing from the original case file.
发现原来卷宗里有几页不见了
And I just couldn't work it out.
我怎么也想不通
Fortunately,
幸运的是
our extremely diligent Archive Officer...
我们的档案官很尽职
found these.
他找到了这个
Go on.
继续走
走啊
You and D.I. Jim Stepton
你和Jim Stepton警探
brought in Nikhail Julian
抓住了Nikhail Julian
for questioning about the murder of Maria Alexandri.
询问他关于Maria Alexandri谋杀案的事情
You interviewed him twice.
你们问询了他两次
What about it?
怎么了
A key witness places him
一位重要的证人指出
walking away from Maria Alexandri's caravan
他在事发当晚
on the night of that murder.
从Maria Alexandri的旅行车走出
Yet you and D.I. Stepton didn't follow this up.
但你和Stepton警探没有进一步追查
Within weeks, Stepton retires
几周之后 Stepton退休
and the case is left unsolved.
这个案件一直悬而未决
Rich?
Rich
And that's when Julian bought you, isn't it?
那时Julian收吗了你 对吧
For the price of a kidney.
以一颗肾的价格
And slickly re-packaged you
他聪明地把你打造成
as his perfect inside man at City Hall.
自己在市政府的内线
What the hell are you talking about?
你们在胡扯些什么
This is completely ridiculous.
真是太荒谬了
Rich! Rich!
Rich Rich
Open the door! Open the door!
开门 开门
Rich! No!
Rich 不
Rich!
Rich
Stop. Cut it out.
停下来 别打他了
Karl Frierson,
Karl Frierson
I'm arresting you on suspicion
由于你涉嫌教唆谋杀Luke Bangura
of soliciting to murder Luke Bangura
和妨碍司法公正
and perverting the course of justice.
我现在对你进行逮捕
Come on, Karl,
得了吧 Karl
you've been in my seat before.
你是从我这个位置上去的
You must know there's nowhere to hide.
你一定清楚 你无处可逃了
We're gonna access your medical records and every piece of correspondence
我们会查看你的医疗记录 以及你与Julian狱长
between you and Governor Julian,
之间的所有通信
because that's who we're talking about, isn't it, Karl?
我们说对了吧  不是吗 Karl
Golding!
Golding
No!
不